

PROFFESSIONAL

My interest in the fourth industrial revolution led me to a passion in web development. My journey began in February 2019 at Naspers labs, when I taught myself how to build a responsible real world website on udemy as well as javascript basics on free code camp. Through Naspers labs, I qualified for a 1 year systems development learnership at Umuzi. Where I learnt fullstack web development technologies and participated in a product team building the umuzi recruitment portal. I am now currently upskilling on python and django. My aim is to one day make a tangible social impact in society, through software development and use these skills to the benefit of the world in general and the african continet in particular.

INTERESTS

- 4th Industrial revolution
- Tech meetups
- Hackathons
- Travelling

PORTIFOLIO



https://github.com/MasixoleMax



https://www.linkedin.com/in/masixo le-menge-b2379118a/

MASIXOLE MENQE

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

FOOD QUALITY CONTROL INTERN JUNE 2017 - JUNE 2018 SEA HARVEST CORPORATION (PTY) LIMITED

- Worked as online-QC (online quality inspections on production floor)
- Conducted internal quality audits
- Product sampling and daily completion of quality control doccuments

QUALITY CONTROL INTERN JUNE 2015 - JUNE 2016 KERRY INGREDIENTS AND FLAVORS SA

- QC-lab inspections in analytical lab and online inspections on production floor.
- Sensory analysis
- Daily upload of production results on system (SAP)

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

NATIONAL CERTIFICATE NQF LEVEL 5 IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY (SYSTEM DEVELOPMENT) (SAQA ID 48872) JUNE 2019 - PRESENT **UMUZI ACADEMY**

BUILD RESPONSIVE REAL WORLD WEBSITES WITH HTML5 & CSS3 MARCH 2019 - PRESENT UDEMY

NATIONAL DIPLOMA IN FOOD SCIENCE & TECHNOLOGY (INCOMPLETE) FEBRUARY 2012 - NOVEMBER 2015 CAPE PENINSULA UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY

TECHNICAL SKILLS





- NODE.JS
- **EXPRESS.JS**
- DJANGO
- SQL (WITH DOCKER AND POSTGRE)
- JAVASCRIPT
- CSS 3 (WITH CSS GRID)
- HTML 5





PostgreSQL





